All right. Now that you've learned
multiple operators, it's time to learn
how to force order of operations. So, if
you remember from elementary school, um
it's please excuse my dear aunt Sally.
Uh parentheses, exponents,
multiplication, division, and then
addition and subtraction. Um
if you want to have that happen in code,
just like when you entered it into a
calculator, you had to use parenthesis.
You have to use parenthesis in your code
as well. So, for example, if I typed
alert
2 * 3 + 4. Um,
and I run this,
I get 10 because 2 * 3 is 6. And then if
I add four, that comes out to 10.
Maybe I wanted it to be 2 * 3 + 4. So in
other words, I wanted it to be 2 * 7. In
order to do that, you use parenthesis.
So I put an opening parenthesis around
the three and a closing parenthesy after
the four. And now it will do what is in
parenthesis first and then it'll do the
multiplication. So if we come over now
we get 14 because 2 * 7 is 14. And that
is how you use parenthesis.